headlinesandheroes.com 2016-12-03

# Headlines & Heroes - Privacy Policy

HEADLINESANDHEROES.COM PRIVACY POLICY  
Updated September 12, 2011

Headlines and Heroes, LLC., the operators of this website: headlinesandheroes.com (referred to as “Company,” “us,” “we,” and “our”) are committed to respecting your privacy and we have created this privacy policy to explain how we use the information that we collect through your use of this Website. Please read this policy and familiarize yourself with its content as it will govern your use of this site. AS A CONDITION OF YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY:

Adults Only  
You must be at least 18 years of age to use this Website for any purpose.

Questions  
If you have questions about this policy please contact us by clicking here.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
We may track the Internet Protocol (IP) address which you use to visit this website and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you voluntarily provide us with your personally identifiable information.

Cookies  
We may use cookies on our site in order to improve your browsing experience by personalizing your experience on our site, providing a streamlined sign-up and login process, determining which portions of our site are visited and tailoring advertising to best serve your needs. Cookies may be placed by an outside company that performs tracking and statistical analysis of visitor behavior pattern, please note that we have no control over third parties and their business practices.

Collection, Use and Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information  
To access some areas of this website you must first register; such registration will require you to provide personally identifying information. Whether or not you choose to provide the information we request is entirely up to you. If you choose not to provide the information which we request, you may be unable to access certain areas of this website or obtain the coupons offered by our site.

If you choose to provide information to us through our online registration, you may be asked to provide your personal information that may include your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other identifying information. We may share the personal information which you provide with our third party processing agents, affiliates and advertisers.

We may collect, use and share your personally identifiable information for any lawful purpose.

We may use the personal information which you provide to send you information, either online or offline, via email, direct mail, SMS text messaging and telemarketing, regarding products or services offered by third-party advertisers. In addition, we reserve the right to rent, sell or share the personal information which you provide with unaffiliated third-parties; these third-parties may use this information for online and offline marketing purposes.

By signing up on our website and providing your personal information you are expressly consenting to receive communications from us and from anyone that we may provide your personal information. In addition, you expressly consent to be contacted in any manner including via email, direct mail, telephone or SMS text messaging, even if your information is listed on the National Do Not Call registry or a similar registry. If you do not agree to these terms than do not use our site.

Finally, we may provide your personally identifiable information in accordance with the law, such as in response to a subpoena, warrant or other governmental request; if we believe it is necessary to protect our rights or the rights of any third party; in the event of a sale, merger, or acquisition; or if you consent to such disclosure.

Opt-Out  
To opt-out of receiving emails from this Website please click here. We will promptly place you on a suppression list for this site and will no longer provide your personally identifiable information to our partners or other third-parties however we cannot stop further communications to you from our partners or other third parties whom we have already provided with your information. Please note that we may still communicate with you regarding site maintenance, changes to this privacy policy or your account.

Accessing and Updating Your Information  
To access, update or delete your personally identifiable information that you have provided to us please contact us by clicking here.

Third-Party Hosting  
We may contract with a third party to maintain and host the Website and to store data collected on the site. Therefore any information you submit, including personal information, may be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by a third-party host. You agree that Company is not liable for any breach of security due to the actions or inactions of the third-party host.

Links to Other Websites  
The Website may contain links to other sites. Any such links are an accommodation to the respective third-party site owners and for your convenience. Sites linked to and from our Website are not necessarily under the control of Company, and Company shall have no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any linked sites, or any link or linking program at any time. Please note that other sites will have their own privacy policies which may differ from this policy and once you enter another site their policy will control your use of that site. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any site that you visit.

Security  
This Website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Changes  
We reserve the right to modify the terms of this privacy policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice on this page. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE WEBSITE FOLLOWING OUR POSTING OF A CHANGE NOTICE WILL CONSTITUTE BINDING ACCEPTANCE OF THOSE CHANGES.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices).
